Let's help the director
run through Xiao Qian's dance.
Get yourselves familiar with the music again.
Okay.
Sure, no problem.
Director,
everyone is ready.
Don't be nervous.
It'll be fine.
Let's start.
Hold on a second.
So,
during that move just now,
it should glide over the head.
Okay.
Let's try that again.
Music!
Hold on a sec.
Director,
that squatting move just now
needs to be a bit faster.
Otherwise, it's easy to fall behind on the floorwork.
Okay.
Let's do it once more.
Music!
Stop.
Feixin,
how do you think I'm doing now?
You've already made some progress.
Xiao Qi,
could you dance a bit slower later?
I can't quite keep up.
Okay.
Director,
should we take a break first?
Okay.
Let's take a break.
Let's rest for a while.
Alright, you can go first.
I need to talk to her alone.
I'll call you if I need anything.
Have a good chat.
The weather is really nice today.
It's been a long time since I saw such a blue sky,
just like when we were in college.
Alright.
I know what you're going to say.
Did you prepare a bunch of words to comfort me?
Are you going to say
when we were studying musicals together,
I was Cast A
and you were Cast B,
so
I'll definitely be fine?
I came all this way.
You've said everything I wanted to say.
It's different, Feixin.
How long has it been since I stood on stage
as a musical actress?
How long has it been since I sang a complete song
and finished a whole dance?
I get nervous too.
Wait a minute.
What did you say?
You're saying that you, Ning Jin,
are worried you won't do as well as me, Bai Feixin?
Are you serious?
Wait a minute.
I get excited whenever you praise me.
I can't forget why I came here.
All right, don't push your luck.
No matter what,
we all believe you can do it.
In my heart,
you will always be the brightest star on stage.
Believe in yourself.
You can do it.
Okay.
Director.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Stop practicing.
Take a break.
No need.
Keep going.
Still practicing?
I want to practice a bit more.
I'll stay with you.
No need.
I'm rehearsing Nie Xiaoqian's solo dance.
I can just practice alone for a while.
Then I'll wait for you over there.
You know what?
Then after we parted, he told me,
Actually,
I've been trying very hard to control myself too.
Then he left.
You know what kind of person I am.
I really wanted to pull him back,
but I...
but I didn't think it was appropriate.
Feixin,
trust me.
I've seen so many of your boyfriends.
I mean, out of all of them,
Leng Yiheng is definitely the most reliable one.
Really?
How could I not know?
Stop talking about it.
If you say any more, I'm going to get nervous again.
Come on, take a deep breath.
Deep breath.
Stop worrying about me.
What about you?
When are you going to make up?
I don't have time to think about that right now.
Besides, even if
I wanted to make up,
do you think he'd still want to?
After all, I was the one who brought up the breakup.
What does it matter who brought it up?
Why are you overthinking this?
The way Jin Xi looks at you right now,
his eyes are dripping with honey.
He'd come running back if you just beckoned him.
Try it if you don't believe me.
It's not that simple.
Think about it.
After our training ends
and I lose my halo,
will he still look at me the same way?
I think Jin Xi likes you,
and it has nothing to do with you being a director.
After spending so much time together,
you must have felt it too.
He's just a very simple person.
You two are the same kind of people.
You two are exactly like the lyrics say,
a match made in heaven.
One lifetime, one pair.
Are you satisfied?
Director.
No.
Xiao Qian.
Turn slower when you get here.
Okay.
Got it.
Xiao Qi,
which outfit should I wear?
This one.
Try it on.
Alright.
Xiao Qi.
Have you guys seen Da Biaojie?
No.
Jiao Ye,
have you seen Da Biaojie?
Right there, rehearsing on stage.
More crisp.
Passing a thousand mountains.
Sorry, Xiao Qi.
It's fine.
You must wait until I turn around to open the fan.
Da Biaojie.
Okay, got it.
Da Biaojie,
Mr. Qiuyu is looking for you.
Just adjust it like this.
Wait for me.
Practice well.
Let's move to the next one.
Director,
wait a minute, Xiao Qi.
Lighting tech, help me check the next cue point.
Okay, Director.
Three, two, one.
As long as there's no problem.
What's wrong, Xiao Qi?
Mr. Qingsong asked
if Jin Xi could go practice the moves with him.
No problem at all.
We've tried it so many times.
You go first.
Jin Xi.
Let's go.
I'll take you to practice the moves with Mr. Qingsong.
Publisher/Producer: Wu Qiming
Director's Special Appearance
Did you get in touch?
Why hasn't he come yet?
We've been waiting forever.
Any luck?
Did you reach Jin Xi?
He's not answering his phone.
He didn't answer mine either.
What about you guys? Any news of Jin Xi?
No.
Nope.
Oh my God.
Don't do anything crazy at a time like this.
Where did he go?
Within half an hour,
if Jin Xi still doesn't show up,
Heying,
you'll play Ning Caichen.
Okay.
I've been ready for a long time.
Sorry.
Pretend I didn't say anything.
Where have you been?
We couldn't reach you by phone.
My phone died, so I didn't get your calls.
Sorry, guys.
I'm late.
Glad you're back.
Everyone,
tonight is our first performance.
I believe you're all ready.
Stay calm and be safe.
Understood?
Understood.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Xiyin Troupe,
let's go!
Let's go!
All departments, get ready.
The audience will be coming in soon.
Where did you go?
I got you a relaxation talisman.
Xiao Qian.
Good luck.
You too,
Caichen.
Don't worry, Mr. Leng.
The Chairman will definitely come.
Here.
Don't tell my Young Master I'm here.
I've been traveling non-stop for three days and three nights.
I haven't had a good sleep.
I was with my Young Master.
Jin Xi.
You really are the male lead
with the worst basic skills I've ever guided.
Take your time.
But you work hard enough.
Forget it.
Since I've arrived at this precious place,
Folks,
what delicious food do you have for me?
Thank you,
Brother Qingsong.
Roast duck.
Alright.
This is delicious.
It makes my mouth water just hearing about it.
Wait.
Come on.
It seems my Young Master is here.
I won't talk to you for now.
I'm leaving.
Right here.
If my soul scatters,
you will also turn to ashes.
Every extra day that scholar spends with you
brings him one step closer to hell.
Xiaoqian.
I don't understand why you won't let me stay here with you.
Swordsman Yan said
I have committed too many sins
and must cultivate in Lanruo Temple for ten years
before I can reshape my physical body.
And during these ten years,
I am not allowed to have any contact with mortals.
Don't worry.
In ten years,
I will definitely come here to get you.
From then on,
we will never leave each other
for the rest of our lives.
Caichen.
For my sake,
you must take good care of yourself.
I will.
Caichen.
See you in the next life.
Xiaoqian.
The ten-year promise has come.
I
have come to see you.
Great!
So handsome!
Jinxi.
This is the surprise I prepared for you.
Great.
Jinxi.
Please welcome
the actor of Black Mountain Demon and the page boy,
Meng Tejiao.
Well done.
Please welcome
the actor of Grandma,
Zhang Wanru.
Please welcome
the actor of Yan Chixia,
Du Heying.
Du Heying is so handsome.
Super handsome, bro.
Please welcome
the actor playing Ning Caichen,
Jin Xi.
Hello everyone, my name is Jin Xi.
Nice to meet you all.
I really hope to join this big family.
Jin Xi,
way to go!
Jin Xi!
Finally, please welcome
the actor playing Nie Xiaoqian.
The director of this play,
Ning Jin.
Director.
I also want to thank
the stage manager of our Xiyin Troupe
and assistant director,
Jiang Xiaoqi.
Xiaoqi, you are the best!
Finally,
I also want to thank my best friend.
Who missed the premiere due to an injury,
the actress who plays Nie Xiaoqian,
Bai Feixin.
You are the best!
Also,
I want to thank all the staff
who worked silently behind the scenes.
Thank you.
Okay.
And thank you to
all the audience members
who have always supported Xiyin.
Thank you.
Xiyin Troupe,
keep it up!
is the best!
We will always support you!
Feixin said her leg injury
will be fully recovered before the premiere ends.
That's great.
If you want to be alone for a while,
I'll wait for you outside.
Ning Jin.
This time,
you didn't hide.
Lights out.